<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Networking on Robert Fleming&#39;s CIT Blog</title>
    <link>https://robertfleming448.github.io/tags/networking/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Networking on Robert Fleming&#39;s CIT Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 17 Feb 2021 23:53:45 -0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://robertfleming448.github.io/tags/networking/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>CIT 480 blog 8</title>
      <link>https://robertfleming448.github.io/post/480blog8/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Feb 2021 23:53:45 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://robertfleming448.github.io/post/480blog8/</guid>
      <description>Introduction In this blog I will talk about all the methods I’ve used to configure my network in order to play multiplayer games with friends. I thought this would be a good addition to a blog I posted two weeks ago as it has similar concepts, where I discussed troubleshooting connection problems with my friends trying to play a multiplayer game. For this blog I will be focusing on the four methods I’ve used to play the popular sandbox game: Minecraft with my friends in the past.
Option 1: The Easiest Yet Least Convenient By far the easiest way to play most PC games with friends is to actually do no network configuration.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CIT 480 blog 6</title>
      <link>https://robertfleming448.github.io/post/480blog6/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Feb 2021 23:53:38 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://robertfleming448.github.io/post/480blog6/</guid>
      <description>Introduction For this blog I actually have something more technical to write about. Since I am a CIT student and this is a fact my good friends are aware of, it is not unlikely for me to be summoned for computer help. In a saga of advice, I have given to my self-admitting technology illiterate friend I aided him in a peer to peer networking issue. I am always happy to help my friends and to stretch my “IT muscles.”
A Little Background I have previously given this friend a lot of advice in the past. Some of this included the ways of running Windows applications on his MacBook.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
