<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>FreeBSD on Robert Fleming&#39;s CIT Blog</title>
    <link>https://robertfleming448.github.io/tags/freebsd/</link>
    <description>Recent content in FreeBSD on Robert Fleming&#39;s CIT Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 14 Apr 2021 17:04:40 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://robertfleming448.github.io/tags/freebsd/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>CIT 481 blog 7</title>
      <link>https://robertfleming448.github.io/post/481blog7/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Apr 2021 17:04:40 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://robertfleming448.github.io/post/481blog7/</guid>
      <description>Introduction In this blog I will go over my recent endeavors in Computer Science 424. For this assignment we needed to build Apache from source and ensure our host operating system could view the website in a standard web browser. Several configuration changes must also be made during build. This includes:
 Multi-Processing Multi-threading  As these are not on by default we must build from source to have a version of Apache that suits our needs This assignment was very open-ended and involved reading documentation to discover a way of accomplishing the task. As a result, the conclusions I came to may not be the most efficient nor the recommended practice.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CIT 481 blog 6</title>
      <link>https://robertfleming448.github.io/post/481blog6/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Apr 2021 11:34:38 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://robertfleming448.github.io/post/481blog6/</guid>
      <description>Preface I am going to try something slightly different this week. As I don&amp;rsquo;t feel that my progress in any one project is substantial nor unique enough to fill the contents of a full blog, I am going to make this blog a double feature The first part will detail my exploits in Terraform to quickly build cloud architecture, and my second part will explain how I setup pf in freeBSD.
Terraform Introduction This part will go over how I created the AWS infrastructure for our group project using Terraform. I was tasked with writing the compute section of our Terraform which includes:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CIT 481 blog 1</title>
      <link>https://robertfleming448.github.io/post/481blog1/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Feb 2021 20:53:24 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://robertfleming448.github.io/post/481blog1/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Despite this being my senior year, and having a relatively light scholastic work-load, I still thankfully have something to write about. I have a backlog of projects that I can dive into should the need arise later in the semester perhaps when things slow down. Additionally, only 2 of my 3 major classes this semester I would consider &amp;ldquo;technical.&amp;rdquo; One of those has little to no coding on a weekly basis. However this week that class has provided me with an opportunity to write down my lab progress. We were tasked with configuring, building, and installing a custom kernel for FreeBSD.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
