<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>AWS on Robert Fleming&#39;s CIT Blog</title>
    <link>https://robertfleming448.github.io/tags/aws/</link>
    <description>Recent content in AWS on Robert Fleming&#39;s CIT Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 25 Mar 2021 13:45:40 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://robertfleming448.github.io/tags/aws/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>CIT 481 blog 4</title>
      <link>https://robertfleming448.github.io/post/481blog4/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Mar 2021 13:45:40 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://robertfleming448.github.io/post/481blog4/</guid>
      <description>Introduction In this blog I will record my issues and solutions I went through while trying to complete the first module of our CIT 481 Senior Design project.
Background Our team is undergoing an alternative project offered by the professor and we are tasked with using an Ansible playbook to automate building a tech stack on an AWS infrastructure. This infrastructure includes 3 private and 3 public subnets spanning across 3 separate availability zones. Each Availability zone must contain a private web server EC2 instance and a public SSH bastion Host EC2 instance. I will focus on the computing resources in this blog and less so on the VPC as that was a lesser role of mine.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CIT 480 blog 9</title>
      <link>https://robertfleming448.github.io/post/480blog9/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Feb 2021 23:53:48 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://robertfleming448.github.io/post/480blog9/</guid>
      <description>Introduction This blog will detail the process I used to complete the fourth lab for CIT 480, in which I configured an AWS EC2 instance to allow communication with an AWS simple storage system bucket. For the most part I thought this lab was pretty straight forward but I did have a minor hiccup which I will detail in a later section.
Background I currently have access to 2 AWS accounts. One is my educate account which still has most of the initial 100 dollar funds. The other is my regular AWS account, which although it does not have any education credits is still within its, first year granting me free tier access to resources.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
