<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>AWS on Robert Fleming&#39;s CIT Blog</title>
    <link>https://robertfleming448.github.io/tags/aws/</link>
    <description>Recent content in AWS on Robert Fleming&#39;s CIT Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 08 Apr 2021 11:34:38 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://robertfleming448.github.io/tags/aws/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>CIT 481 blog 6</title>
      <link>https://robertfleming448.github.io/post/481blog6/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Apr 2021 11:34:38 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://robertfleming448.github.io/post/481blog6/</guid>
      <description>Preface I am going to try something slightly different this week. As I don&amp;rsquo;t feel that my progress in any one project is substantial nor unique enough to fill the contents of a full blog, I am going to make this blog a double feature The first part will detail my exploits in Terraform to quickly build cloud architecture, and my second part will explain how I setup pf in freeBSD.
Terraform Introduction This part will go over how I created the AWS infrastructure for our group project using Terraform. I was tasked with writing the compute section of our Terraform which includes:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CIT 481 blog 5</title>
      <link>https://robertfleming448.github.io/post/481blog5/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Mar 2021 17:37:47 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://robertfleming448.github.io/post/481blog5/</guid>
      <description>Introduction As mentioned in the blog prior where I discussed Load Balancers and Certificates on AWS, this week I will be going over my solution for getting our SSH bastion to function as intended.
SSH Bastion As a preface, an SSH Bastion is a remote server that resides in a public section of a network. By connecting to this node, you can further connect to other machines located in private, non-internet facing subnets.
Server Setup An ssh bastion really is very similar to any other machine out there. All that really matters for our implementation is having a network with a private and public subnet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CIT 481 blog 4</title>
      <link>https://robertfleming448.github.io/post/481blog4/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Mar 2021 13:45:40 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://robertfleming448.github.io/post/481blog4/</guid>
      <description>Introduction In this blog I will record my issues and solutions I went through while trying to complete the first module of our CIT 481 Senior Design project.
Background Our team is undergoing an alternative project offered by the professor and we are tasked with using an Ansible playbook to automate building a tech stack on an AWS infrastructure. This infrastructure includes 3 private and 3 public subnets spanning across 3 separate availability zones. Each Availability zone must contain a private web server EC2 instance and a public SSH bastion Host EC2 instance. I will focus on the computing resources in this blog and less so on the VPC as that was a lesser role of mine.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CIT 480 blog 9</title>
      <link>https://robertfleming448.github.io/post/480blog9/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Feb 2021 23:53:48 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://robertfleming448.github.io/post/480blog9/</guid>
      <description>Introduction This blog will detail the process I used to complete the fourth lab for CIT 480, in which I configured an AWS EC2 instance to allow communication with an AWS simple storage system bucket. For the most part I thought this lab was pretty straight forward but I did have a minor hiccup which I will detail in a later section.
Background I currently have access to 2 AWS accounts. One is my educate account which still has most of the initial 100 dollar funds. The other is my regular AWS account, which although it does not have any education credits is still within its, first year granting me free tier access to resources.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
